Welcome back to the arena.
So far in this season, you have done the deep work of discovery to create your inner blueprint.
You have architected your M.V.P. and you've started to activate it in the real world, conditioning
your resilience and agility.
Now we arrive at a pivotal moment where strategy meets action in the most structured way possible.
This lesson is where we pull it all together and into a tool that we truly use to elevate
your performance, the 90-Day Way Personal Brand Action Plan.
A study from Dominican University found that people who write down their goals are 42%
more likely to achieve them.
Why?
Because the act of writing it down is the first step in creating a system.
It's not just about setting goals.
It's about having a system to achieve them consistently.
This is what the 90-Day Way provides.
Today we will explore the prerequisites for your success, show you how to identify and
address your most critical gaps, and then guide you step by step in building your first
90 Day Plan.
The A.R.A.W. pillars we are conditioning are alignment and wellbeing, ensuring your plan is both
purposeful and sustainable.